Kevin Munar

SOFTWARE ENGINEER

Kevmunar@hotmail.com | **in** linkedin.com/in/kevinmunar/| **©** github.com/yomoon93| **♦** 3477382556 | **Q** Queens, NY

SUMMARY

ADAPTABLE RECENT COLLEGE GRADUATE WITH A COMPUTER DEGREE

RR, WITH WORK EXPERIENCE. AIMING TO LEVERAGE THE ACADEMIC EXPERIENCE AND PROVEN KNOWLEDGE OF WEB DESIGN, WEBSITE ARCHITECTURE, AND PROGRAMMING TO SUCCESSFULLY ADD VALUE TO YOUR COMPANY. FREQUENTLY PRAISED AS FOCUSED BY MY PEERS, I CAN BE RELIED UPON TO HELP YOUR COMPANY ACHIEVE ITS GOALS.

SKILLS

FRONT END: HTML5, React.js, CSS3, JAVASCRIPT, JQuery BACK END: JAVA, C++, Node.js, Express, SpringBoot DATABASES: SQL, Oracle, Postgres DB, MySQL, MongoDB,

TOOLS: GitHub, XCode, Eclipse, Atom, VS Code, MatLab, UNIX, Microsoft Office

JOB EXPERIENCE

IT Specialist - The Trade Desk - Manhattan, New York

July 2021- Present

- Install and update company software and hardware as needed.
- Provide direct support to users across the organization.
- Helping set up hardware, software, diagnosing connectivity and data access problems, answering questions about hardware or software, and helping users access shared drives and devices.

Per Scholas- Software Engineering Learner - Bronx, New York

March 2021 - July 2021

- Developed a Ping Pong game using JavaScript (github.com/yomoon93/MOD1Project)
- Developed a site that fetched API data using JavaScript & React (github.com/yomoon93/JeopardyHW) & (https://github.com/yomoon93/HomeWork/tree/master/SoftwareEngineering/htmlJS/PizzaRat)

Nanov Display - Technician Intern- Brooklyn, New York

Nov 2020 - March 2020

- Perform preventive maintenance and calibration of equipment and systems which led kiosks working at optimal levels
- Wrote reports and recorded data on Kiosk equipment and specifications to assist engineers with problems that the Kiosk might have
- Traveled to fix Kiosks at multiple sights which led to customers getting accurate data

AlexaPath - Front-End Developer Intern - Brooklyn, New York

Sept 2018 - Jun 2019

- Lead in the design of company's website using various technologies, including JavaScript which helped gain leads for people who wanted to buy the product
- Determined coding requirements for site creation and implemented ideas from the team.
- Maintained website using Github, and backed up files for instant recovery in case of problems
- Tested website and troubleshooted prior to live deployment which led to high productivity

EDUCATION

New York City College of Technology

Aug. 2018 - May 2020

B.S. Degree Computer Engineering

- Created a robotic arm that used a frequency divider with an internal clock that was 50mHz. this allowed to control the robotic arm using pulse width modulation to control servo motors. Using a field- programmable gate arrays which was part of the DE2 board. We were able to code and control the servos motors by using switches and buttons.
- Using sensors and an Arduino microcontroller programmed a self-sufficient plant